Welcome back in this world, we're going to make wireframe for our project that is that offered online
full order application, so you can see the application is look like this.
This is the final project.
So let's create a wire frame for it.
Let's create a new page.
Click on the plus icon.
So these are applied.
So let's rename it.
So first of all, we are going to need frame, you can press F or you can go into this section and choose
frame and select iPhone 11 Pro Max frame.
So in first frame, we only want to show the brand name that is left of it.
So let's clear some components for it.
First, let's make some more frames.
OK, our five frames are created now.
So first frame is going to be our brand name page, and the second one is signing face, then third
one in sign up page and in fourth frame.
We are going to add like a fourth we can order food is there like burger pizza and fried chicken and
all that.
So I think we don't need a fifth trip.
So let's do this one.
If the frame rate on your keyboard.
The frame is different now.
So we have all frames now.
Let's make some components select the rectangle, draw the angle, like this ad or text?
So it is going to be our brand name.
The font is too small.
Select the font, go to design panel and increase the font of two local politics.
OK.
I just want.
And the center.
So this is our first component.
So select the both the rectangle and the text to select the multiple things you know that we have to
hold, shift and press the text and the rectangle are selected now and we have to press control G to
make a group.
So if I move like this, then bolting together, let's say you don't make a group on this.
First of all, I neutral on this.
OK, so if I move this?
You can see the brand name is not coming with this tangle.
That's why we grouped them.
So for grouping Celebrity Angle, you hold shift celebrity and press control.
And this is now a group, so if I like a more like this on the screen, you can see the mood things
are going to get less May goes down.
So I told you how to make component, select your element and go to Bomberman and select this one button.
And now this is your component, so you can use them multiple times in your project, and you can also
access to this asset when you can see the brand name.
Let's make a second component that is going to be our image.
Let's choose rectangle.
The shortcut is are.
And let's make a perfect square hole shift.
Like this, and let's earn some.
What do you want him?
You can see the color of Polygon and the square is gray, so we have to change the color of Polygon,
so to do that, select the Polygon Go and redesign panel, click on the field and let's move this closer
to us.
White like this?
This smallest one like this.
OK, let's duplicate this one.
OK.
Michael, from this side of the mountain, and let's make a small.
Some.
Okay.
Like this, we have to also change the color of their skin onto whites like this.
OK.
So this is our image and select all the things and press control.
So this thing is group now and let's make this.
Element into component.
So this is our second component.
So let's make a profile picture.
Component four.
We are going to use Circle so we can price or we can use this ellipsis button.
Moist air from this imagine.
First of all, we need to.
Make it small.
Now let's add this image into this segment, or we can see the image is not visible because it is in
the images selected.
Click right on it and you can see the option been to front.
And you can see the images now in front like this and select all of the things from press control gene
to group them is now grouped and let's make a component.
OK, this one is a component now.
So this element is for profile picture.
Let's make sign in and sign up Bar Navigation Bar.
For that, we are on a new rectangle.
Let's make sure it's not just with our frame, so it perfectly matches with our screen.
I think we have to dig a little bit.
Now, let's add a text image.
First on its signing.
And the second one is sign up.
So let's align them together, set all the things for us to take the sign in the rectangle.
Now select the sign up button.
Now go to design Bennett and let's first and then bottom novelists align them vertically.
OK, it is now.
So next thing we have to make is that logging button and a button, so that sort of distress lubricated
by pressing art.
And the first one is going to be our logging.
I forgot to make this navigation bar into component.
Select all the things control G and select only just one button.
So this thing is not component, let's make this page also a component.
Duplicate this burden and remember to.
Sign up.
So this is our last component, and we are going to need some major buttons like hamburger or some icons
like Facebook, Google and Twitter.
Intimate library really, really showed you.
We installed some icon packages so we can use this.
Use them in this project.
So to access those things, go to Assad and click on this book icon.
You can see for the Icon Plus actor.
Click on this toggle button.
You can see we can use this icons, so we need this hamburger menu icon.
So let's more.
This one, and you can also search.
Like Facebook, Twitter.
And so long as we were.
But it is not available so we can use.
Other icons, like all of this is.
OK, we now have these four icons.
Let's make our wireframe.
So we created all the components, so we are going to use them in our bathroom.
So in front page, we have to add a brand name.
So I'm going to.
Drank this like this, let it just it vertically okayed it, and just now, let's rename it into like
brand.
And second, he's is going to be signing.
And the third one is a line of which.
And the last one is men.
OK, so we have four pages now.
The first one is done so in second frame.
What I want to do is that I want to an image on the top.
So let's try like this.
And I also want to put a brand name on this image, so let's track this endless ad running.
So our, you know, will know so this image and this is the brand name.
I think the color is the same, so we have to change the color and the branding.
So let's select the master component.
Let's make it more darker like this.
And this makes finding page so we are going to regret this action murder.
So next, we want to like username, so let's draw a line.
So we need to lines the first one is for username.
And the second one is for.
Password and, uh, uh, we have to earn a log in button.
Or more towards the second frame like this, and let's end our log in with buttons.
Those are Facebook, Google and we don't.
So let's lend them together first, so let's make them bigger.
First is going to be Facebook, second is going to be Google.
So let's align them together, select Facebook, Hold Shift, Select Log and select Trudeau.
First, we have to add just the bottom.
And lest I them vertically.
OK.
And let's earn some horizontal spacing.
So these things are aligned.
So in this space, we have a problem.
So our under a will not know.
This is the sign up with your sign in page because all things are the same.
So what we can do is that we can make this signing which bold so current it is regular.
Let's make it bold.
OK, now our new will last.
This is the sign in page, so next page we have to make.
Same thing.
Those are like this brand name.
We also have to use these images, so I'm going to copy this, but the things?
We are almost done the the only thing is remaining is that.
Our main page, so on the main page.
So he was at is log in now.
So let's make his profile icon.
Let's air the hamburger menu.
This one, I think we have to increase the size of it.
Who learned what was the last frame like this?
So let's align them together, hold shift.
Select the profile icon.
Plus bottom and the second is vertical.
OK, let's add a text called.
Let's make some categories.
So we only have three categories, like what is going on with Visa and told Vanity.
So the list Adam, image for it.
Or.
Let's make it smaller.
And let's allow them to get the whole shift to the second instead of the third one that's at the bottom.
And then vertical and let's add some horizontal spacing.
OK.
So I just like this, OK?
And this are some text and silly categories or.
And lest we never turn to both those degrees, different sides.
Hold dragged to the second category.
And let's remember turning to pizza.
And the third one is.
So let's align the fault together.
Now it is a line together, so let's move them.
Legitimate upward, so.
OK.
This is perfect.
And so currently we are on like, uh, let's see, currently we are on burger you.
So let's make this image little bit below.
So currently in Bogut, currently we are in Burma section, and let's say we have only two options for
the US in the first page.
Just make another one like this, and let's make this image bigger because.
The user will know.
Currently, we selected this bill, and we can also make this text a bold.
So our developer will know currently the customer is on the BOGO section and we can earn some prizes.
For it, like, oh, let's see, this burger is for.
$15 doesn't give the -- sites.
For the $15.
Let's make it up to like twenty four and for second.
But let's make it up to like $18.
I know these are quite expensive.
Let's make it normal.
Because the user is selected the first blogger.
And this is the text.
A board like this.
Okay, so let's add some sections of it, so our user will know we have more options.
And select the first circular list in the California.
So our director will no doubt our customer will.
Currently, he or she is on front page.
So if he swipes, then he's going to be on the second page like this.
I was like, I S. So this is the wireframe for our first project.
That is the light of the project.
You can see our final project.
This is our brand name.
You can see brand name plus image.
Log in, sign up.
Username, password logging and logging, which button select widow, his book and Google.
Same for here.
You can see we also so this logging into like Benkler, because our users will know.
Currently, he is on the logging page and in this page.
He will launch his own sign up page, and we can see the categories be the puzzle that you can and you
can see.
We made this burger.
Highlighted.
So user will noncurrent he's on a category, and first he selected this burger, the first on it and
it is $15 burger and you can see I also added the card so he can check out the profile picture and hamburger
mean.
And we can also add the surge, but.
So this is the wireframe for our first project.
So in next winter, we are going to make this vital frame into this project.
I know this is the very individual, but we just have to drag and drop things and I just do some portion
of the element like this.
So once we make you aware of, you can make your project melt faster.
So I'm going to divide every video in the separate part, like in first video, I will add this blessed
in analog and faith.
In the first video and the second video, I will add a sign up page and in turn, I will add this main
page, which will become more Shorter's, and it will also going to be easy to understand.
So that's what will do, and I will do it next one.