Welcome back.
And previously we met this frame.
Now let's make a UI for our app.
So what a home.
Create a new team, let's name it.
You can name it whatever you want.
So currently, I'm naming it led to a project one create team.
So I'm currently working, so I'm going to skip for now.
So currently I'm using Freewheelin.
That's why I'm going to choose choose starter if we have professional plans that you can choose them.
So just click on starter so you can see our team name and the color of our team.
Now let's go to wireframe and let's move this.
Welcome to our team.
You can see the color of our team and the team project.
OK, our file is not.
Click on Team Project.
You can see our wireframe.
I think we are going to need this sort of drill this one.
And click on Team Project and click on Plus button and design for.
So we won't be thinking the world frames look different because I accidentally deleted that previous
frame, so that's why I created this bathroom again.
So that's why it looks different.
So let's rename it.
Let's choose a frame.
Press f choose iPhone 11 Pro Max.
So anywhere from you can see the first images for our brand name, so that is lightweight.
So let's create that first frame.
This arrangement?
OK, you can name it whatever you want.
So let's choose a text.
OK, let's increase the font size of this text.
To like 64.
OK.
And let's change the font.
And too sensitive, a solicitor in the middle.
OK, Lisa Lindisfarne was the vertically and then horizontally located alignment and the center.
Select the frame and listen to a lot it.
Though currently, the color is white, so I'm going to choose the red so currently resolved, so let's
make it gradient.
So a choose linear.
Can the second pillar into poplin?
Or we can choose any color you want.
There's increased opacity of the second pillar.
OK, now it looks cool.
So if you want, you can adjust your gradient like this.
OK, that looks cool.
OK, I think I slept a different font, so save the font.
And this is the one we required for this project.
OK.
So that's all I need to together.
Vertically and horizontally at the same time.
OK, Linda, let's make it white.
So it will look more better like this.
OK, our first frame is greater now that is brand name page, so you can see in the wireframe.
This is the brand name, and this is the pitch.
So in this world, we are going to create this signing page.
So the secretary and others within the next one.