Welcome back, In Bruges, where we met this random page, so in this video, we are going to make signing
pitch.
So let's choose a frame.
iPhone 11 Pro Max.
OK, like this president admitting to like signing.
So as you can see in wireframe, we place the image, so we are on a blitz image, but in different
format.
So let's make a circle and the shortcut it's all and draw it on the frame like this.
Let's make it up to like four hundred fifty.
I think we have to make it beyond that image.
Let's make it up to 70.
OK.
OK, let's do the edges so you can see there's a gap.
This move towards the right like this.
OK, so the so-called the alert just make it clear to the linea and the first ballot is going to be
our vertical.
And the second pillar is going to be our wet weather like this.
OK, let's close this down.
OK, now we have surplus, so let's duplicate this circuit, so the so-called whole world and drag it.
Like this and select the circle.
Go to our tool and choose blessed image.
And let's choose this bizarre image.
Open.
And let's place it on these first ellipse.
So after placing emerge, select the circle this one and let's move on the frame.
Like this, let alone it together, OK?
And does it in the circle so a lesser degree, the city of two, like 70 to 80 percent less to 70 percent.
OK, this looks good.
And you can see in wireframe, we bless the brand.
So that has led to fertile.
This jagged.
Select the brand name holder and mood on the.
So you can frame like this.
OK, OK, let's integrate the form sites up to like shipping
and list and just hitting the center.
OK.
Like this?
This looks cool.
OK, now let's make this sign in navigation more.
So I'm going to use the different method for it.
This a rectangle.
Back this.
I think I have to interpret a little bit.
OK and less island and desanto.
OK, it is in the center now, the upward.
So let's change the ages up to like thirty five.
And now let's change the color of each into white.
So let's have some effect like drop shadow.
OK, let's add some settings.
Let's make blood up to 15.
And Spirit up to two.
Why?
What's going to be why?
OK, now this looks cool, so let's make a log in and sign a button.
So let's choose a rectangle.
I added some dimension, you can see the word is 264 and height is fortify and extend what position?
You can see here.
So let's make it the sharp corner into round.
Let's make it up to 13.
Let's do this shape.
Make it up to help.
And listing the color of it, let's make you like, Oh, let's choose this popcorn.
And splits it on the top of this, OK, like this?
OK, let's change the color of that worship.
Let's make it white.
Najib Grange.
OK.
Like this?
OK, let's zoom effect, click on effect so you can see the drop shot is adding.
I think it's it's look OK, so I'm going to leave as it is.
So let's make a taste.
The first one is going to be logging.
The currently the font is sensitive one, so let's change it into like five minutes.
And let's make for couple.
Let's add just a phone, according to this tape.
OK, it is in the center now.
So let's duplicate this text on, let's make it final.
So we've got to do this totally right, so that's why it is not possible to select the font.
Let's make it black.
Or if you only you can choose this color.
He does not look cool unless I learned unless I did it manually.
And dismantle.
OK.
Like this, I think this is just a bit.
OK, now this looks good.
You find Zoom out.
You can see the interface of design and pace, it looks like this.
So let's make username password, so go to shapes.
Choose the line.
And let's make it all here.
Unless and just less entangle into zero societies in the middle.
OK, it is in the middle and let's do a dissembling on Earth.
Drag it down.
Let's add some text like email.
OK, let's decrease the foreign sites up to like 10 and adjust the text.
Let's change the color of this text.
And also the color line.
Just make it look like this one.
And let's change the color of this line also.
Got a stroke, and I think cholesterol cylindrical, and let's make it.
Like this one?
Select email and user model donors and listen to the password and also change the color of this line.
Now, let's make forward passwords so that this possible text or the old.
Closer to you.
Scientists like this just make logging button less copy this.
Shape, I think, is going to be fine.
OK, let's change the color of it.
Currently, it is kind of gray.
Let's make it appear like this.
And I think this font, which you.
That's all I need to get a.
Well, the thing is, it was in shift.
Bottom horizontal, located in the center, no.
So listing that type of font connected is regular.
So let's make it semi bald, so it will look more cool.
OK, like this?
OK, what else remaining?
So we can see in wherefrom we made everything, so only things are remaining like this.
Log in with buttons.
OK, let's add them from the local files.
OK, let's import those.
As to the defiance, OK, let's do the judo for us as group them together.
So why are we are grouping them?
Because these are the HPC players.
Let's say I want to go in somewhere so we can see the if I select on this iconic, I see the victory
selector.
So it is going to be a mismatch with our project.
So that's why we are grouping with it.
If I selected this whole thing and include them together, it was in control G.
So the group now and if I click on this, you can see I can move it wherever I want.
So let's dig into this one.
Good idea the height of all the logos of Twitter and Facebook like just to heighten the weight.
And so for Facebook.
And also for good.
So we are adjusting weight and height, so it is I just know this because then one of my one.
The one thing remaining is that we have to earn attached that is all natural to this statute and hold
it and dissenter and let's make it cost less and just seem to center.
The figure was a really smart document really going to tell you that at the center of it and also the
spacing in between the tankless increase the font size up to like, well, OK, our signing pages are
ready now.
So in next video, we are going to create a sign up page.
So that's it for 2012, and I was in the next one.