Previously, we managed to sign him first, so in this video, we are going to make a sign of page.
So let's select this frame signing page and two speech.
Like this and listing image and to sign up.
So you can sign up as we have to change things you can see in the wireframe, the things like we have
to change the sign up button, we require some extra lines like on phone password and also we have to
change the sign up.
So let's make those changes.
OK, let's first, let's change the color of this font.
Currently, it's kind of low level, so let's make it.
White.
And let's move this rectangle.
On the right side.
OK, additional.
So let's turn the color of the logging, so currently, despite the make you this color, OK?
OK, now what we have to do is that we have to add one more line and it is going to be our password.
So let's move this forward password.
That's a good downward.
Like this and this copied this line.
Let's copy this password and this line.
Holder trended downwards.
OK, what password is greater now?
OK, let's align them together, select human hold shift, select all the things password dump on password
and this last line, and go to a line setting and click on more options and choose.
This should be what you call spacing.
OK.
It is a line now.
I can see you.
So let's move this forward password, little --.
Of course.
OK.
Like this.
So currently, we are on a sign up, it's changing to sign up.
Let alone it horizontally, we can see it is alone in the center, no.
So one thing is determining that some icons like you might seen some apps where you have the eye symbol
audio McGillis are those eyes go to S8 like on this dream library.
And toggle this feather icons.
And search for I.
OK, you can see the symbol.
So it was this one.
So let's decrease the size of it up to like this, like 60.
So let's change the color of it, currently, it is black.
So we are going to choose this.
A little simpler of this password.
And acidic or drug, you don't sign up bridge and so on.
Gone from fast food.
So the only the last thing is remaining, that is the main page.
You can see the wire free market.
So in the next hour, we are going to make that ways.
So that report really good analysis of, hasn't it?
Next one.