Welcome back.
Previously, we made to sign up.
So in this building, we are going to make this main page so you can see the wire frame for it to choose
a frame.
iPhone 11 Pro Max your listing image.
OK, let's make this pitch digital with Gray, because we are going to add some elements like search
bar and also if the search bar is going to be white, so.
So it is not going to.
So I think there's going to be in the.
And the list in the background and like totally.
Like this.
So our mental page will be more visible, so for this mental bridge, you can see in the wire frame,
we require this hamburger menu icon, the profile picture icon and text and some images.
So let's make those things.
So in my folder, I have all the resources.
So let's move them into our.
Sigma project.
OK.
The images are like 2B, so we have to consider them.
So we have all the resources, like this hamburger menu icon that can handle the profile picture and
some elements like a disposable.
So we are going to use one by one for less and just this menu at the top.
So less question route and the length and it'll.
So the second thing is profile picture, so let's make that profile vigil, OK.
For that, we are going on need ellipse and horseshoe and go to the chapel and place image.
And I going to do this one, you can choose your own image also.
And I'm going to put it on this open, OK, I see it is closed, but you can see the photo is kind of
on the right side.
It is infinite and you can see in the fail option, we have this image.
Click on it.
And indeed.
And let's choose Grow.
And this is the image like this, and OK, the profile picture, it's really.
So this are some stroke, it stroke.
Let's make it up to to change the color of this stroke.
The White.
And less recited.
You like.
Do you mind?
OK, so let's add some text that is.
Choose the food you love.
So this one will see it in the text.
And controls we.
OK.
So you can see I used on the.
Falcons want and all.
For this upper, I use the regular and the and for this cordial, I used the same word.
So let's add it.
According to this, the icon.
Like this?
So what is the next thing we have to do so we can add categories like this?
We can do that, but let's earlier search bar.
So where users can find these items?
So select the rectangle.
We can just copy this ship so that the ship and drag it on the supreme.
OK, so let's change the color of it into white, and you can see we already have some drop shadow,
so we can, if you want to, we can adjust it.
I'm going to leave as it is, so let's edit text.
So let's select this text.
Austrian imaging to search less and less chance of color of it currently is black.
So I'm going to choose according to this search.
Text like this must decrease the size of image.
And this all together.
OK, so it is a now deciding what to let's make the said what a bit bigger, so let's make it great
appeal to hockey.
And does it center in the scientist is such and such, I can't.
OK, the next thing is to add categories.
So let's add some categories.
OK.
Let's add some categories.
So the rectangle.
And draw it like this.
Let's make it up to like worth up to one 10 one one zero.
And the height of the next 70.
And let's add some advantages.
Let's make it up to like a quantify.
So looking at this one again or last one?
So let's Linden together.
So let's change the color of which.
Let's make it a white.
If you want, you can also add a drop shadow in you.
Let's change the color of that background.
Currently, the whitest non-visible light my.
Are these accounts OK?
These are the you find.
So let's move them together out, control G.
Second one spins out of control key.
Germany, Japan and control.
So when we are working with them, so they are not going to mismatch.
OK, the first one is one of Ebola, and the and the first section is gender dimension of it, like,
oh, let's queue up to like fifty or forty five.
So let's add to them at the center.
OK.
They are alone now.
OK, what else is remaining?
So we have to name it like woke up is changing the soil a strange image.
So let's name it the first puzzle.
So I'm going to copy this text.
This island in Bermuda.
So click on the Pogo Centre, the second and select the pizza, then the bottom.
OK, now I'll end them vertically.
Thanks.
So we have to change the color of this burger because currently we are.
The burger section so we can change the color of it.
So users will know is in the burger section.
So let's move this category and this.
S. Little bit moles, of course.
Currently, we are in BOGO section, so we are going to air this.
So let's do the rectangle and draw rectangle like this.
Let's give the damage like one certainty and height of like
two one zero.
Let's add some religious side up to let thirty point.
OK.
So this one is going to be our first global alert to get this one.
So I'm going to like increase the height of it because currently the user selected this burger.
So let's make it up to let's 119 it.
Sulking like this, and let's change the color of it, let's make it clear, don't.
Let's change the first bill into red and skin color into global.
You can place it wherever you want.
As per requirement.
So I'm going to blessing it all here.
Like this?
OK?
Let's and the image of that burger.
So currently, this is the first burger.
And it's in the color of the white.
This is going to be also Ken Vogel, let's just name them.
So the first one, I don't know what is the name of them, but we can name in court you, what do you
want?
Or you can search on the Google, the name of the police.
I can call them over here.
So let's change the color of this font.
It is black.
Let's make it white.
So it will look more better.
Is the -- sites?
Nothing.
And let's make it simple.
And this and the price of it, Senator, this text holds.
And as our dollar sign.
This is burglaries up to like $18.
Almost the length to text.
Make it up really pretty.
So if you want to, you can also add writings in it.
So let's earn the trading.
I think I having the resources.
Let me let me say OK, or I have this dance intro for the project.
OK, you can see the start.
And let's change a lot of it into a law like this.
So users will know all previous customers had good experience with disposable.
Selling them together, so last name this burglar currently distorted words.
So therefore, it is not possible, so let's make it.
Black this.
OK, so unless mortgage or you.
And this includes the -- sites of, let's say.
And then just copy this one.
Just change the color of it also.
Analysts say the value of it, so it is going to be up to like $15.
OK, what else is remaining?
I think the auditing is done, so I think this listing ceremony, so selection of souls and those things
to the ellipse.
Blogs and sermons.
Let's make it like this Gray.
So if the first not and let's it failed or we can choose this.
Hello.
On this, make a little bit bigger, so.
User Bill Law is in the food time.
OK, like this.
That's all we have got together.
And I think one thing is everything is there to add a card, so let's select the ellipse and show all.
Let's give her a of electric pump.
And all Irish folk.
And this tender inner pillar of grit and into.
In asset holder, we have that you can see the back.
So this ad is back shopping bag and the center, so.
And let's change the color of it, but let's make it right.
And do this artistic the center.
OK, thank you.
So everything is done.
So our main obsession is done now.
So the only thing is remaining in this project is there to do the right thing.
So in the in the next world, we are going to do protecting.
So that's opportunity.
And I was you guys.
Next one.