Welcome back in Brazil, we met this man who paid, so one thing is remaining for this project is there
to do prototyping so.
So I'll show you how to do prototyping so you can pause the video and do on your own or if you don't
know how to do it, so you can continue the video.
So I assume you done that part.
So let's do the programming for this project.
Let's go to the panel and you can see this wide shot.
And when I hold over it, it becomes a plus.
I can click on it and drag it on the sign in page so you can see this menu will be purple.
So this is don't a detailed panel.
So you can see we have options like aren't so currently listed on tab and navigate to same page.
So we are navigating from Ben Page to signing page.
So it is, it is OK.
So if you want, you can add an image in it.
So currently, let's go with instant.
And I think that's it.
Now click on the same page.
So you can see we have options like logging in a sign up, let's say, users and installing this app
called First Time, so he want to go to the signup page so he can click on the sign a button.
So let's do it.
Interaction.
So we can see in the interaction, judges are never going to sign up page and the animation is instant.
Let's say it was a race like have already happened and accidentally touch on the sign up button.
So here you want to go back on the login page or sign in page so he can go back by using this login
button.
So let's less what interaction and navigate to and which all these things will be same for it.
So we don't have to change anything.
Audio.
Then let's say it was reported similarly and the password and you want to go to the main menu page.
So let's give the interaction to this button.
OK, from Logan Page, you will go on the main page.
And also the same with design a button.
From sign up, he will go on the main page after putting all the details like us username, Emily,
password and password.
I think we're done here.
When I click on the this blank space, we will get these options.
So from here, if you want to change the device, you can change it from here.
So currently I am choosing this iPhone 11 Pro Max, so select this one.
And if you want it in the model or you can do it from here, currently it's gold.
You can choose silver, space gray green like this and it will show the preview.
And if you want to change the background color of it, you can do it from here.
So currently it is black again, like you would any color you want.
Like this?
So let's go with white, so it doesn't matter.
You can choose any color so you can see here we have horizontal and vertical orientation.
If you want to change it into horizontal, you continue like this or portrait.
So let's go with the portrait and let's click on this present button.
You can see our is presenting and the present icon over here on the top.
But.
OK, you can see the first brand page, if I click on this, we will get on the sign in page.
After that, if I click on this blank space, you can see we get two hot kids.
Those are like a sign up and log in page.
Let's say I'm a new user and I want to sign up, so I'm going to tap the sign up button and I can put
my details like username, password and confirm password.
And after that, I can sign up.
So I can also beg on the log in page if I want like this and let's click on logging.
So we're on it so I can order is boggle from you.
If you want to, you can let go animation to these pages.
If we click on this, sign up.
You want to do animation like a moving or mortar push so we can do it from here.
Let's choose a movie and you will see the little interaction over here.
And you can also join the time over there, currently with 300 milliseconds and the animation is in
is ithout format.
OK, let's pretend this one.
You can press are to restart this application from the beginning.
So I'm going to press ah on the keyboard so you can see our landing page.
OK, so let's click on this sign up.
We can see that move in effect audio.
Let me show you one cool thing.
So let's go to Grant Page Random page.
Click on this arrow Typekit arrow.
And currently we are on on tab.
So let's go to our smart animation audio and let's live up to like a gender militant and we can change
it like argue in direction like aren't about entourage while hovering and all that.
Let's just like a while holding onto Mouse Center and let's pretend is less press are to restart.
And if I would like a out of my most or this app, you can see that animation.
Let me do it again.
You can see that animation.
So let's change a little bit like go order, and let's increase the name up to 500 milliseconds.
And this president yet again to restart.
And on tap, you can see the animation become a bit slow.
Like this.
So because of this are smart animation, we get that cool effect.
So I will let go.
Set it over like Boyd Holding.
And let's make it up to victory and putting two hundred looks very cute.
And let's go to within reach.
Press of when I like into my mouth on the Ellis brand page, you can see the interaction.
The brand name goes on the top.
And if I leave this app, you can see this again comes to the random page and I can do in direction
directional here.
Like, sign up.
OK, that you can see that in effect, and you can go to the sign up page if you want to, you can add
animation to dismantle base.
Let's add some animation on the page.
Circling the sign up page, follow this arrow, and let's say I had a mission, so let's try this design.
OK.
And let's Britain this one, let's hit our.
Log in.
OK, sorry.
He tore sign up page.
And from and from sign up basically giving that effect.
OK.
It looks really cool.
It is fully.
I think it is very in effect.
Has argued that any mission to the log in button also.
OK, let's hit our.
And Long Beach property, that is all different.
If you're only going to use a machine like smart animation, so let's choose a smart animation and let's
broaden the screen, hit our.
Logging, you can see that cool animation, audio, smart animation that looks cool so you can set any
animation you want.
So it depends on you and when you do, that also depends on your project.
So this is where we complete our project one.
Let's see if you are struggling with this project.
We have to watch our video again and again to do this project.
So if you made this project, we can share this project on the Instagram or Twitter.
And you can also take me or there.
So in the next project, we are going to make a movie website or you can say, like a streaming service
application like Netflix, Amazon Prime.
So that's me signing off.
Thanks for watching, and I was already in the next one.